AoM Records 5593
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series G. Miscellaneous
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 14)
      Includes Constitution of Fellows Group
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      Memo from Alvin Brown
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 16)
      Membership List
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      Fellowship Nominations
    - Fellows Nomination, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 18)
      17-Jun-65
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management Statement of Policy, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 20)
      Minutes of the 1966 Meeting
    - Fellows Group Membership List, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 21)
      Aug-75
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management (Box 99, Folder 22)
      Membership Roster
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 24)
      Correspondence: Constitutional Changes
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Statement of Mission
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Fellows Dinner Minutes, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      Elections for Fellows, Correspondence
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      Nominations for Membership
    - Fellows of the Academy of Management, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      Mailing List
    - Fellows of the Academy, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      Minutes of Annual Dinner
    - Fellows Group, 1974-1975 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Fellows Group, 1974-1983 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Institute for Administrative Research (IAR), Correspondence and History, 1964-1965 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1967-1969 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - IAR, Correspondence and Material, 1974-1976 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - IAR, Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - IAR, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 25)
      Research Proposal Awards, "Admin. Research in Health Care"
    - Institute for Administrative Research, Research Proposal Awards "Admin. Research in Health Care", 1977 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Letterhead and Stationery (Box 101, Folder 1-6)
    - Policy Manual Revised, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Policy Manual Final Version (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Policy Brochure (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Policies and Procedures Manual, Academy of Management (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Policy Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Policy Manual, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Policy Manual, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      Includes: constitution, bylaws, organization, fiscal policies, secretarial-administrative policy, election procedure, membership policies, AM journal, professional divisions, annual meetings, Fellows policy, historical records
    - Policy Manual (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Policy Manual, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Resumes and Biographical Sketches (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Resumes, B-D (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Resumes, E-K (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Resumes, K-L (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Resumes, M (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Resumes, M-R (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Resumes, R-S (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Resumes, W-Y (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Territorial Domain Statements, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Territorial Domain Statements (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - American Risk and Insurance Association, Memos and Financial Statement (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Paper, "A Profile of the Academy of Management Members" (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, Certificates, etc. (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Series II. Publications
  - Sub-Series A. Correspondence Concerning Academy's Publications
    - Jr. Editor, Paul M. D'Auten, Jr, 1956-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Jr. Editor, Dalton McFarland, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Jr. Editor, Dalton McFarland, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Jr. Editor, Dalton McFarland, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Jr. Editor, Dalton McFarland, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Jr. Editor, Paul J. Gordon, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 6-10)
    - Jr. Editor, Paul J. Gordon, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 1-3)
    - Jr. Editor, Paul J. Gordon, 1966 (Box 104, Folder 4-7)
    - Jr. Editor, Stanley Vance, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 8-11)
    - Jr. Editor, Stanley Vance, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
    - Jr. Editor, Stanley Vance, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 5-11)
    - Jr. Editor, Stanley Vance, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 1-3)
    - Jr. Editor, William G. Scott, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 4-9)
    - Jr. Editor, William G. Scott, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 1-4)
    - Jr. Editor, William G. Scott; Stanley Vance, Editor, Newsletter, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 5-11)
    - Manuscript Revisions (ed., Scott), 1971-1972 (Box 108, Folder 1-12)
    - Jr. Editor William G. Scott, John B. Miner (Box 109, Folder 1-12)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1-4)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 5-7)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 1-6)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner; Review Editor, Max Wortman, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner; Review Editor, Max Wortman, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner; Review Editor, Max Wortman, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 1-7)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner; Review Editor, Max Wortman, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 1-8)
    - Jr. Editor, John B. Miner; Review Editor, Max Wortman, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Jr. Editor, Larry Cummings; Review Editor, John Slocum, 1978-1979 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Jr. Editor, John Slocum, 1980-1981 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Review files (correspondence, manuscripts, page proofs, etc.), 1982-1985 (Box 115-119, Folder All)
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1957-1964 (Box 120, Folder All)
      August 1957 - September 1964
  - Sub-Series B. Publications (Journal, Review, Executive, Newsletter) and Miscellaneous
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1964-1968 (Box 121, Folder All)
      December 1964 - March 1968
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1968-1972 (Box 122, Folder All)
      September 1968 - December 1972
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1973-1975 (Box 123, Folder All)
      March 1973 - June 1975
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1976-1982 (Box 124, Folder All)
      December 1976 - December 1982
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1983-1984 (Box 125, Folder All)
      June 1983 - December 1984
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1985-1986 (Box 126, Folder All)
      March 1985 - December 1986
    - Academy of Management Journal, 1987 (Box 127, Folder All)
      May-87
    - Academy of Management Review, 1981-1984 (Box 128, Folder All)
      October 1981 - January 1984
    - Academy of Management Review, 1984-1986 (Box 129, Folder All)
      April 1984 - April 1986
    - Academy of Management Review, 1986 (Box 130, Folder All)
      Oct-86
    - Academy of Management Executive, 1987 (Box 130, Folder All)
      February 1987, May 1987
    - Academy of Management Newsletter, 1971-1987 (Box 131, Folder All)
      3 folders of miscellaneous publications
    - "Study on Organizational Behavior" (Box 132, Folder All)
      includes questionnaires
    - Papers Presented at 1983 Annual Meeting (Box 133, Folder All)
- Series III. Miscellaneous
  - Keith Davis, 1960-1985 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1968 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - AoM Correspondence, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - AoM Recommended Changes to the By-Laws and Constitution (Box 134, Folder 10)
- Ken Davis - Award - Instituto Chileno de Administracion Racional de Empresas (Box 135)
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 136)